// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct identifier?",
    answer: "VAR_123",
    options: ["$var_name", "VAR_123", "varname@", "None of the above"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is the address operator?",
    answer: "&",
    options: ["@", "#", "&", "%"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "The programming language that has the ability to create new data types is called___.",
    answer: "Extensible",
    options: ["Overloaded", "Encapsulated", "Reprehensible", "Extensible"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "Which of the following is the original creator of the C++ language?",
    answer: "Bjarne Stroustrup",
    options: [
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Ken Thompson",
      "Bjarne Stroustrup",
      "Brian Kernighan",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The C++ language is ______ object-oriented language.",
    answer: "Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented",
    options: [
      "Pure Object oriented",
      "Not Object oriented",
      "Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented",
      "None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "C++ is a ___ type of language.",
    answer: "Middle-level language",
    options: [
      "High-level Language",
      "Low-level language",
      "Middle-level language",
      "None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Which type of memory is used by an Array in C++ programming language?",
    answer: "Contiguous",
    options: ["Contiguous", "None-contiguous", "Both A and B", "Not mentioned"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What did we call an array of the one-dimensional array?",
    answer: "Single-dimensional",
    options: [
      "Single-dimensional",
      "Multi-dimensional",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Which of the following can be considered as the object of an array?",
    answer: "Elements of the Array",
    options: [
      "Index of an array",
      "Elements of the Array",
      "Functions of the Array",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many types of elements can an array store?",
    answer: "Same types of elements",
    options: [
      "Same types of elements",
      "Char and int type",
      "Only char types",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
];
